const SportsJokesData = [
    {
        id: "1",
        question: "What did the baseball glove say to the ball?",
        answer: "Catch ya later!"

    },
    {
        id: "2",
        question: "What are the rules for zebra baseball?",
        answer: "Three stripes and you’re out."

    },
    {
        id: "3",
        question: "Why are umpires always overweight?",
        answer: "It’s their job to clean their plates."

    },
    {
        id: "4",
        question: "Which baseball player holds water?",
        answer: "The pitcher"

    },
    {
        id: "5",
        question: "How do baseball players keep in touch?",
        answer: "They touch base every once in a while."

    },
    {
        id: "6",
        question: "Why can’t basketball players go on vacation?",
        answer: "They aren’t allowed to travel."

    },
    {
        id: "7",
        question: "What do you call twelve millionaires gathered around the TV to watch the NBA Finals?",
        answer: "The Chicago Bulls"

    },
    {
        id: "8",
        question: "Why can't Aaron Rogers use the phone anymore?",
        answer: "Because he can't find the receiver."

    },
    {
        id: "9",
        question: "Why do the Germans always get beat by the Canadians in hockey?",
        answer: "Canadians bring the “eh” game, while Germans bring their wurst."

    },
    {
        id: "10",
        question: "What do soccer referees send during the holidays?",
        answer: "Yellow cards."

    },
    {
        id: "11",
        question: "What does a Dallas Cowboys fan do when his team has won the Super Bowl?",
        answer: "He turns off the PlayStation."

    },
    {
        id: "12",
        question: "Why don't the Cubs have a website?",
        answer: "They can't get 3 W's in a row"

    },
    {
        id: "13",
        question: "Whats the difference between the Chicago White Sox and a mosquito?",
        answer: "A mosquito stops sucking."

    },
    {
        id: "14",
        question: "Does anyone know what they call winning teams in Chicago",
        answer: "Visitors"

    },
    {
        id: "15",
        question: "Why do Packer fans smell so bad?",
        answer: "So blind people can hate them as well."

    },
    {
        id: "16",
        question: "Trump's favorite baseball team is the Yankees",
        answer: "Except during the draft, then it's the Dodgers."

    },
    {
        id: "17",
        question: "How do you keep the Detroit Lions out of your front yard?",
        answer: "Put up goal posts."

    },
    {
        id: "18",
        question: "Why did the young boy ask his parents to take him to the Cowboys’ AT&T Stadium during the tornado warning?",
        answer: "He said, “There’s never a touchdown there."

    },
    {
        id: "19",
        question: "Why didn’t your neighbor’s dog want to play football?",
        answer: "It was a boxer."

    },
    {
        id: "20",
        question: "Why didn’t your neighbor’s dog want to play football?",
        answer: "It was a boxer."

    },
]

export default SportsJokesData;